jetsmart.com 2019-11-02

# PRIVACY POLICY JETSMART General Considerations

                                      PRIVACY POLICY
                                          JETSMART
General Considerations
At JETSMART we are committed to transparency, security, and strict compliance with
regulations on privacy and protection of personal data of our users and customers.
For the purposes of this Privacy Policy and the terms and conditions of use of the website
described therein (hereinafter the "Privacy Policy"), the term "JetSMART" shall include
JetSMART Airlines SpA, a company established under the laws of the Republic of Chile,
and/or JetSMART Airlines S.A., a company established under the laws of the Republic of
Argentina, and/or their subsidiaries or agencies in the countries in which they operate, as
the case may be.
Without prejudice to the foregoing, the owner of the website and Responsible for
Processing the information collected by JetSMART is the following company:
        JetSMART Airlines SpA
        Rol Único Tributario N° 76.574.879-8
        Domiciled at Avenida del Valle Sur 650, Office 61, Ciudad Empresarial, Huechuraba,
        Santiago de Chile
        Telephone: 600 600 1311
        Contact email: privacypolicy@jetsmart.com
Use of the Website
Before using this website (www.jetsmart.com) (the "Website"), we encourage you to read
and agree to the following terms and conditions
The use of this Web Site, as well as the services offered or provided through it, are aimed
at people with the necessary capacity to enter into legally binding contracts, either directly
or with the prior authorization of a third party. Consequently, access to the Website,
interaction or contracting of services in any form by minors must have the express consent
and supervision of their parents or legal representatives.
If you do not accept this Privacy Policy, you may not use the Website and/or its content in
any way, and you must exit immediately.
The use of this Web Site, as well as the services offered or provided through it, implies the
full understanding and express acceptance of this Privacy Policy.

Content and Intellectual Property
Unless otherwise indicated, the products and services that may be commercialized through
this Web Site will only be available in the territories indicated therein, and all advertising
contained in the Web Site is exclusively intended for the markets corresponding to such
territories.
This Web Site, and all its contents, including photographs, videos, brochures, designs,
musical compositions, etc., are protected by copyright, and are the exclusive property of
JetSMART, or have been duly licensed for use on the Web Site.
The brands included in this Web Site are protected in the territories where they are
commercialized. Labels, logos and other distinctive signs included on this Web Site are the
property of JetSMART, or have been duly licensed for use on the Web Site. Their
unauthorized use is sanctioned civilly and criminally by the laws of the State of Chile, and
other courts where they are recognized.
The user of this Website acknowledges the existing rights over the materials included in it,
as well as JetSMART's ownership of them. Any use of the materials included on the Web
Site is strictly prohibited, without the prior express written permission of an authorized
representative of JetSMART.
The information contained is provided "as is" on this Web Site. Without prejudice to the
provisions of applicable law, JetSMART is released from any liability, and excludes any
warranty associated with this Website and its contents, either in terms of its operation or
the information contained therein, provided by JetSMART, its affiliates or third parties,
including any inaccuracy or omission in the information provided by this Website, or with
the documents available on it, except for any obligation and / or warranty imposed
expressly by applicable law.
Links to Third Parties
JETSMART expressly states and informs users that while browsing the Website they may be
directed to other sites which are not under its control. In fact, there are links to other sites
other than the Web Site, which take the user out of the scope of our service and
responsibility. JETSMART does not guarantee or accept any responsibility for errors or
omissions in the content of other sites, or for viruses, malware or any other direct or indirect
damage arising from the use of other sites or their content.
The contents of other websites linked from this Website are the sole responsibility of their
owners. JetSMART does not monitor or review the content of websites that are linked from
this Website. The opinions expressed, or material provided on such sites are not necessarily
shared or promoted by JetSMART and are the sole responsibility of third parties in charge
of them.

Website Operation
Except for the obligations and guarantees expressly imposed by applicable law, JetSMART
is not responsible for any damage or loss to the user caused by failures in the operation of
the Website, the server or the Internet. Users may not hold JetSMART responsible or
demand payment for lost profits, by virtue of damages resulting from technical difficulties
or failures in software, systems or the Internet. JetSMART does not guarantee continued or
uninterrupted access and use of the Web Site. The system may not be available due to
technical difficulties or Internet failures, or any other circumstance beyond JetSMART's
control. In such cases we will try to restore it as quickly as possible without thereby being
held responsible.
Use of Cookies and Web Beacons
Cookies are files or information that a Web site transfers to and stores on a computer's hard
drive when browsing a particular website or Internet portal, allowing the storage of users'
preferences, helping to identify the areas that are most and least popular, learning about
interests, behavior, demographics, and other information related to those who visit or are
users of the website, and thereby better understanding their needs and interests and
providing them with a better service or related information. Many of the developments and
updates are based on information provided by cookies. The use of cookies on the Website
allows JETSMART to customize the Website pages to meet the needs of users. Users
expressly authorize JETSMART to store and use cookies in the aforementioned terms, and to
analyze the pages they navigate and the searches they carry out, in order to improve their
commercial and promotional initiatives, show advertising or promotions, banners of
interest, personalize contents, presentation and services, and for any of the other uses that
users authorize in accordance with this Privacy Policy regarding their personal information,
among others.
On the other hand, Web beacons are images that can be embedded in pages and websites
and which have a purpose similar to cookies. Additionally, a Web beacon is used to measure
user traffic patterns from one page to another in order to maximize how traffic flows
through the web.
The user can disable cookies through the navigation menu. Most browsers are set to accept
cookies. If the users prefer, they can configure their browser to reject them or to notify
them when they are received. However, it is possible that part of the sites or the Web Site
may not function properly if the user disables cookies. On the other hand, JETSMART
declares that it does not and will not use spyware, adware or any other similarly intrusive
software on its website.
Users expressly authorize JETSMART to use Cookies and Web Beacons on the Website.
Privacy

The information obtained by JETSMART is provided voluntarily by its users, who expressly
accept and authorize JETSMART to use it in accordance with this Privacy Policy and
applicable legislation.
Users voluntarily and expressly accept the processing of their personal data in accordance
with this Privacy Policy. Consequently, the user's personal information may be processed
and stored, both in Chile and in other countries. Without prejudice to the foregoing, your
personal information may not be disclosed for purposes that are not allowed by applicable
law.
JETSMART is entitled to collect all personal information provided for these purposes and
authorized by the user through its Website and / or from other sources, and may collect,
store, use, circulate, delete, transmit and / or transfer their personal data.
JETSMART receives and automatically stores the information that users provide when
browsing the Website, when using online services, whether by accessing it, ordering or
buying products, participating in promotions and offers, registering as a user on the Website
and / or via email, among others. This includes all information posted in forums, surveys,
chat groups or comments through which the user interacts on the Website. It also includes
any other way in which the user relates to JETSMART or by virtue of which they purchase
any product or service, or any other information provided by the user to JETSMART through
other channels, such as web pages associated with the Website, social networks, Contact
Center, during the Check-In process or baggage check-in, whether carried out at the airport,
online or remotely, through their participation in surveys, e-mails, requests, among others.
The information collected in accordance with the preceding paragraph, without the
following enumeration being exhaustive or limiting in any way, includes or may include the
users' full name, postal address and/or domicile, marital status, occupation, nationality,
gender, telephone number, identity card and/or passport number, e-mail address, IP
address and other computer or computer information, photographs, videos and multimedia
or audiovisual material, opinions, preferences, destination information, commercial history,
history of means of payment such as credit and/or debit cards, and other personal data, as
well as all kinds of information related to the profile of each user.
JetSMART is authorized to collect the user's e-mail address and to use and display the user's
full name and e-mail address for purposes of communicating with them, as well as for
notifications and the delivery of information related to the services offered by JetSMART.
Users may at any time request not to receive further communications, for which the means
to cancel the respective subscription will be provided.
In general, personal information submitted by the user will be intended to provide the
service described on the Website, to improve the user experience, better tailoring its
features and performance, and to provide additional information, such as promotions from
our partners and advertisers. Likewise, their information will be used for the following

purposes (i) reservation of tickets and optional services, (ii) modifications to the contract,
(iii) cancellations and changes of itinerary, (iv) refunds, (v) handling of queries, complaints
and claims, (vi) membership in the discount club or other loyalty programs, (vii) accounting
records.
Their personal data may be used by third parties who are providers of JetSMART and who
provide services (under strict conditions of confidentiality and security), to provide some of
the services and features available on the Website, and to enable smooth communication
with users; these third parties may include, but are not limited to, reservation and
distribution systems, contact centers (call centers), representatives, travel agencies, agents
or intermediaries of the carrier and third party providers of these services, which may be
supplied in countries other than the place where the reservation takes place.
Any personal information obtained by JETSMART by the means described herein will be
handled in accordance with the provisions of this Privacy Policy and in accordance with
current legislation. This Privacy Policy does not extend to information that, according to the
law, does not constitute personal information, is provided by third parties, or to practices
carried out by such third parties.
Personal information obtained by JETSMART under this Privacy Policy will remain in its
databases no longer than the time necessary for the purposes for which such information
was collected. In this sense, personal information will be deleted by JETSMART when it is
no longer necessary or relevant for the purpose for which it was obtained, and any period
of storage of information that is legally required or necessary to comply with the law has
expired, and without prejudice to the authority of its owners in this matter, as set out
below.
JetSMART may disclose the personal information of its users when this is required to comply
with the regulations that apply in the countries where it operates, a legal or judicial order
imposed on JetSMART, including the protection and defense of its rights, or third parties.
Rights and Obligations of Information Owners
Users who hold their personal data shall have the following rights: the right to know, update
and correct their personal data, the right to request proof of the authorization granted to
the Controller, the right to be informed of the use of their personal data, the right to file
complaints with the competent authorities for breaches of personal data protection
regulations and the right to revoke their authorization and/or request the deletion of their
data.
Information owners can use their rights to know, update, correct and delete information
and revoke the authorization, through a written request to JetSMART addressed to the
email privacypolicy@jetsmart.com

Users' requests for personal information that are made in accordance with the provisions
of this paragraph will be solved as soon as possible by JETSMART and, in any case, within
the deadlines established by law to do so.
On their part, users guarantee and are responsible, in any case, for the veracity, accuracy,
validity and authenticity of the personal information provided and agree to keep it properly
updated, without prejudice to the power of JETSMART to update it ex officio. JETSMART
shall not be liable in any way for any direct or indirect damages and/or claims that may arise
from personal information provided by its users and/or owners in an incorrect, inaccurate,
equivocal or incomplete manner. The user is banned from providing illegal, threatening,
defamatory, pornographic, obscene or any other material or information that could mean
any risk and / or civil or criminal injury.
Applicable Law
The laws applicable to this document shall be those corresponding to the relevant legal
territory and, in the absence thereof, the laws of the State of Chile.
If any part of this Privacy Policy is determined to be invalid or unenforceable under
applicable law, the provision deemed invalid or unenforceable shall be deemed superseded
by a valid and enforceable provision that most closely reflects the intent of the original
provision, and the remainder of this Privacy Policy shall continue in full force and effect.
Changes to the Privacy Policy
JetSMART reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy and its terms and conditions, from
time to time, as it deems appropriate or to adjust to new regulations, and agrees to
communicate any changes to users and owners of personal information in a timely and clear
manner, in accordance with applicable law. Continued use of the Website will mean your
acceptance of any adjustment to this Privacy Policy.
Security
JETSMART has adopted security levels to protect personal information in accordance with
applicable law and has deployed all reasonable technical means and measures at its reach
to prevent the loss, misuse, alteration, unauthorized access and theft of personal
information provided by users. Notwithstanding the foregoing, users are aware that such
security measures are not impregnable and, consequently, they release JETSMART from any
damage that may arise from these circumstances and that is not directly attributable to
JETSMART, in accordance with current legislation. However, in the event of any security
incident affecting personal information, JETSMART agrees to take such action as may be
reasonable and required by law to inform the owners and the competent authority by the
most expeditious means possible, and to take all reasonable measures to reduce the
damage that may result from this circumstance.

Specific regulations on Personal Data Protection
JetSMART is obliged to respect the provisions of Article 19 No. 4 of the Constitution of the
Republic of Chile and Law No. 19,628 of the Republic of Chile on the Protection of Personal
Data. JetSMART also agrees to respect the provisions of Laws No. 12.965 and No. 13.709 of
the Federative Republic of Brazil on the use of the Internet and the Protection of Personal
Data, as well as the applicable laws of the Republic of Colombia, Peru, Argentina, and any
other country where JetSMART operates.
In compliance with Resolution 14/2018 of the AAIP of the Argentine Republic, it is hereby
announced that the AGENCIA DE ACCESO A LA INFORMACIÓN PÚBLICA ("AGENCY OF
ACCESS TO PUBLIC INFORMATION"), in its role as the Control Body of Law No. 25,326 of the
Argentine Republic, has the power to deal with complaints and claims filed by those who
are affected in their rights by non-compliance with current regulations on the protection of
personal data.
Section 6 of Law No. 25,326 of the Argentine Republic, states: When personal data is
collected, the owners must be expressly and clearly informed beforehand of: a) The purpose
for which they will be processed and who their addressees or class of addressees may be;
b) The existence of the file, register, data bank, electronic or of any other type, in question
and the identity and domicile of the person responsible; c) The mandatory or optional
nature of the answers to the proposed questionnaire, especially with regard to the data
referred to in the upcoming article; d) Consequences of providing the data, the refusal to
do so or the inaccuracy of the same; e) The possibility of the interested party to exercise
the rights of access, correction and deletion of data.
In accordance with Law No. 13.709 / 2018 (General Law on Data Protection - LGPD for its
acronym in Portuguese) of the Federative Republic of Brazil, it is incumbent upon the
National Data Protection Authority to implement simplified mechanisms, even by electronic
means, for the submission of complaints regarding the processing of personal data that do
not comply with LGPD.. Access to and use of this Web Site implies full and express
acceptance of these terms and conditions, especially for the purposes covered by section 7
of Law 13.709 of the Federative Republic of Brazil.
Santiago, [●] September, 2019
JetSMART ©2017 All rights reserved.
